<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>  <DATAPACKET Version="2.0"><METADATA><FIELDS><FIELD attrname="Code" fieldtype="i4"><PARAM Name="PROVFLAGS" Value="7" Type="i4" Roundtrip="True"/></FIELD><FIELD attrname="Identifier" fieldtype="string" WIDTH="25"/><FIELD attrname="WhenToLoad" fieldtype="string" WIDTH="15"/><FIELD attrname="Type" fieldtype="string" WIDTH="9"/><FIELD attrname="Attributes" fieldtype="string" WIDTH="80"/><FIELD attrname="Text" fieldtype="bin.hex" SUBTYPE="Text" WIDTH="10"/></FIELDS><PARAMS CHANGE_LOG="14 13 8 15 8 8 16 15 8 9 0 2 10 0 2 11 0 2 12 0 2 14 0 2" READONLY="TRUE" DEFAULT_ORDER="1" PRIMARY_KEY="1" LCID="1033"/></METADATA><ROWDATA><ROW Code="1" Identifier="defAngelica" WhenToLoad="NoCache" Type="whdroplet" Text="&lt;p&gt;Angelica is a genus of Apiaceae, some members of which are grown as a flavoring agent and for their medicinal properties. The most notable of these is Angelica archangelica which is commonly known just as Angelica. Sea watch, Angelica lucida, has been eaten as a sort of &quot;wild celery&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Angelica is a biennial umbelliferous plant that only grows leaves during its first year, and a fluted stem that grows up to two metres tall during the second year. Its leaves are composed of numerous small leaflets, divided into three principal groups, each of which is again subdivided into three lesser groups. The edges of the leaflets are finely toothed or serrated. The flowers, which blossom in July, are small and numerous, yellowish or greenish in colour, are grouped into large, globular umbels, which bear pale yellow, oblong fruits.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Angelica archangelica grows wild in Finland, Sweden and Norway, mostly in the northern parts of the countries. It is cultivated in France, mainly in the Marais Poitevin, a marsh region close to Niort in the départment Deux-Sèvres.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;h2&gt;Usage/History&lt;/h2&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;From the 10th century on, angelica was cultivated as a vegetable and medicinal plant, and achieved great popularity in Scandinavia in the 12th century and is still used today, especially in Samic culture. A flute-like instrument with a clarinette-like sound can be made of its hollow stem, probably as a toy for children. Linné reported that Samic peoples used it in reindeer milk. Other usages include spices.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&lt;p&gt;In 1602, angelica was introduced in Niort, which had just be ravaged by the plague, and it has been popular there ever since. It is used to flavour liqueurs or aquavits (e.g. Chartreuse), omelettes and trout, and as jam. The long bright green stems are also candied and used as decoration.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;h2&gt;Etyomolgy&lt;/h2&gt;&#010;&lt;p&gt;&#010;Archangelica comes from the greek word &quot;arkhangelos&quot; (=arch-angel), due to the myth that it was the angel Gabriel who told of its use as medicine. In Finnish it is called väinönputki, in Sami faddnu or fadno, in English garden angelica, in German arznei-engelwurz, in Swedish kvanne and in Norwegian it has the name kvann.&lt;/p&gt;"/><ROW Code="2" Identifier="defBasil" WhenToLoad="NoCache" Type="whdroplet" Text="&lt;p&gt;Basil (Ocimum basilicum, Lamiaceae) is also known as Albahaca, St. Joseph&apos;s Wort, and Sweet Basil. It is a tender annual herb.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Holy basil (Ocimum sanctum = O. tenuiflorum) is a sacred herb in India but is not much used for culinary purposes there. Known as Tulasi, the plant is worshipped as dear to Vishnu in some sects of Vaishnavism. A tea made from the leaves is used as a remedy for cold in India. Also known as Thai basil, it is a very common ingredient in Thai cuisine with a strong flavor similar to aniseed, which used to flavor curries and stir-fries.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The most commonly used basil varieties are sweet basil and Thai basil. Other varieties include Purple Ruffles, Mammoth, Cinnamon, Lemon, Globe, and African Blue.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Basil is a low-growing annual. It has light green silky leaves and tastes somewhat like cloves, with a strong, pungent, sweet smell. Basil is very sensitive to cold.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The word basil (fr. Gk basileus, king) means &quot;royal&quot;. The Oxford English Dictionary quotes speculations that basil may have been used in &quot;some royal unguent, bath, or medicine&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;h2&gt;Basil as a herb&lt;/h2&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The fresh herb can be kept for a short time in plastic bags in the refrigerator, or for a longer period in the freezer, after being blanched quickly in boiling water. Place fresh leaves in a dry jar with a pinch of salt, and cover with olive oil. The dried herb tastes utterly different, rather like curry.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Mediterranean cuisines frequently use basil, especially combined with tomato. Basil, often the &apos;Genovese&apos; variety, is one of the main ingredients in pesto - an Italian sauce from the city of Genoa.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;There are several varieties of basil grown in many regions of Asia. Most of the Asian basils have a clove-like flavor that is generally stronger than that of the Western basils. Basils are very popular in Thai cuisine. Vietnamese and Chinese also use fresh or dried basils in soups and foods.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Some culinary writers have opined that basil is the &quot;king of herbs&quot;.&#010;&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&lt;h2&gt;Cultural aspects&lt;/h2&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The name basil may derive from the basilisk (also fr. Gk basileus), a legendary monster, because the plant was said to be a cure for its poison. Indeed, A Modern Herbal, by Mrs. M. Grieve, tells us: &quot;The seeds have been reckoned efficacious against the poison of serpents...&quot;&#010;&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The plant has frequently been considered poisonous itself, while African legend claims it protects against scorpions. European lore sometimes claims that basil is a symbol of Satan, though in other places, like India, the plant is highly revered. Similarly, it is a symbol of love in present-day Italy, but represented hatred in ancient Greece.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;In Boccaccio&apos;s Decameron a memorably morbid tale (novella V) tells of Lisabetta, whose brothers slay her lover. He appears to her in a dream and shows her where he is buried. She secretly disinters the head, and sets it in a pot of basil, which she waters with her daily tears. The pot being taken from her by her brothers, she dies of her grief not long after. The story is already told of the Longobard queen Rosalind.&lt;/p&gt;"/><ROW Code="3" Identifier="defBergamot" WhenToLoad="OnFirstUse" Type="whdroplet" Text="&lt;p&gt;Bergamot Orange (Citrus bergamia or Citrus aurantium (bitter orange) ssp. bergamia) is a citrus fruit, small and roughly pear shaped. It is sour and its aromatic peel is used to produce oil of bergamot, which is used in Earl Grey tea. The fruit, produced in Italy, is a cross between the pear lemon and the Seville orange or grapefruit.&lt;/p&gt;&#010;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Bergamot (Monarda didyma) is a North American aromatic herb also known as Scarlet Monarda, Oswego Tea, or Bee Balm. Its name is derived from its odour which is considered similar to that of the orange. The scientific name comes from Nicolas Monardes who wrote the first American flora in 1569. The name &quot;Oswego Tea&quot; comes from the Oswego Indians who taught the immigrants how to use it for tea after the Boston tea party in 1773.&lt;/p&gt;"/><ROW Code="4" Identifier="PGDICTIONARY" WhenToLoad="OnFirstUse" Type="whpage" Attributes="desc=&quot;Dictionary Entry&quot;" Text="(~mcdoctypehtml~)&#013;&#010;&lt;html&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;head&gt;&#013;&#010;  (~drHead~)&#013;&#010;&lt;/head&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;body&gt;&#013;&#010;(~drPageBegin~)&#013;&#010;&lt;div id=&quot;whdemopagecontent&quot;&gt;&#013;&#010;(~JUMP|pgEnterDBHTML|[Back]~)&#013;&#010;&lt;h1&gt;Definition of Term: (~command~)&lt;/h1&gt;&#013;&#010;(~DYNCHUNK|def,(~command~)~)&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Content copied from Wikipedia.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;(~JUMP|pgEnterDBHTML|[Back]~)&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;!--- whdemopagecontent --&gt;&#013;&#010;(~drPageEnd~)&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;"/><ROW Code="6" Identifier="n/a" WhenToLoad="Preload" Type="whmacros" Text="mckey1=mcvalue1&#010;mckey2=mcvalue2"/><ROW Code="7" Identifier="PGCACHINGCHOICES" WhenToLoad="NoCache" Type="whpage" Attributes="desc=&quot;About the caching choices implemented in this demo&quot;" Text="(~mcdoctypehtml~)&#013;&#010;&lt;html&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;head&gt;&#013;&#010;  (~drHead~)&#013;&#010;  (~drStyleDL~)&#013;&#010;&lt;/head&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;body&gt;&#013;&#010;(~drPageBegin~)&#013;&#010;&lt;div id=&quot;whdemopagecontent&quot;&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;h1&gt;(~pagedesc~)&lt;/h1&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;dl&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;dt&gt;PreLoad&lt;/dt&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;dd&gt;These items are loaded into memory when the WebHub application first runs (before any pages are requested).&lt;/dd&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;dd&gt;Macros should always be set to PreLoad.&lt;/dd&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;dt&gt;OnFirstUse&lt;/dt&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;dd&gt;These items are loaded into memory the first time they are requested by a site visitor.&lt;/dd&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;dt&gt;NoCache&lt;/dt&gt;&#013;&#010;&lt;dd&gt;These items are not saved in memory, regardless of how many times they are requested by a site visitor.&lt;/dd&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;/dl&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;/div&gt;  &lt;!--- whdemopagecontent --&gt;&#013;&#010;(~drPageEnd~)&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;"/><ROW Code="8" Identifier="drStyleDL" WhenToLoad="OnFirstUse" Type="whdroplet" Text="&lt;style&gt;&#013;&#010;dt { font-weight: 700; }&#013;&#010;dd {margin-bottom: 2em; }&#013;&#010;&lt;/style&gt;"/><ROW RowState="1" Code="11" Identifier="defCinnamon" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="(~waRetrieve.execute|defCinnamonDetail~)"/><ROW RowState="2" Code="12" Identifier="defCinnamonDetail" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="(~waRetrieve.execute|defCinnamonPart1~)(~waRetrieve.execute|defCinnamonPart4~)"/><ROW RowState="2" Code="13" Identifier="defCinnamonPart1" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="&lt;p&gt;(~waSETLOCAL|cinnamon=&lt;strong&gt;Cinnamon&lt;/strong&gt;~) (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~) (~waRetrieve.execute|defCinnamonPart2~)&lt;/p&gt;"/><ROW RowState="2" Code="14" Identifier="defCinnamonPart2" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="(~waSETLOCAL|cinnamon=(&lt;i&gt;Cinnamomum zeylanicum&lt;/i&gt;) ~) (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~) (~waRetrieve.execute|defCinnamonPart3~) "/><ROW RowState="2" Code="15" Identifier="defCinnamonPart3" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="is a small evergreen tree 10-15 m tall, belonging to the family Lauraceae, and a spice obtained from the inner bark of this species. It is native to Sri Lanka. The leaves are ovate-oblong in shape, 7-18 cm long. The flowers, which are arranged in panicles, have a greenish colour and a rather disagreeable odour. The fruit is a purple 1 cm berry containing a single seed."/><ROW RowState="1" Code="16" Identifier="defCinnamonPart4" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="(~waSETLOCAL|cinnamon=cinnamon~)&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon is principally employed in cookery as a condiment and flavouring material, being largely used in the preparation of some kinds of chocolate and liqueurs. In medicine it acts like other volatile oils and once had a reputation as a &quot;cure&quot; for colds. The pungent taste and scent come from cinnamic aldehyde or cinnamaldehyde.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The best (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~) is from Sri Lanka, but the tree is also grown at Tellicherry, in Java, Sumatra, the West Indies, Brazil, and Egypt. Sri Lanka cinnamon of fine quality is a very thin smooth bark, with a light-yellowish brown colour, a highly fragrant odour, and a peculiarly sweet, warm and pleasing aromatic taste. Its flavour is due to an aromatic oil which it contains to the extent of from 0.5 to 1%. This essential oil, as an article of commerce, is prepared by roughly pounding the bark, macerating it in sea-water, and then quickly distilling the whole. It is of a golden-yellow colour, with the peculiar odour of cinnamon and a very hot aromatic taste. It consists essentially of cinnamic aldehyde and, by the absorption of oxygen as it ages, darkens in colour and develops resinous compounds.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon has been known from remote antiquity, and it was so highly prized among ancient nations that it was regarded as a present fit for monarchs and other great potentates. It is mentioned in Exodus 30: 23, where Moses is commanded to use both sweet (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~)  (Kinnamon) and cassia, and in Proverbs 7: 17-18, where the lover&apos;s bed is perfumed with myrrh, aloe and (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~). It is also alluded to by Herodotus and other classical writers.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Being a much more costly spice than cassia, that comparatively harsh-flavoured substance is frequently substituted for or added to it. The two barks when whole are easily enough distinguished, and their microscopic characteristics are also quite distinct. When powdered bark is treated with tincture of iodine (a test for starch), little effect is visible in the case of pure cinnamon of good quality, but when cassia is present a deep-blue tint is produced, the intensity of the coloration depending on the proportion of the cassia.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Culpepper&apos;s Herbal advises a daily draught of (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~) in &quot;any convenient liquor&quot; against scurvy. Studies have found that using half a teaspoon of (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~) a day significantly reduces blood sugar levels in diabetics. The benefit, which can even be produced by soaking (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~) in tea, also benefits non-diabetics who have blood sugar problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;WebHub note: the purpose of this &quot;cinnamon&quot; example is to demonstrate one technique of creating variables that are local to any named piece of W-HTML.  Please see the web actions named &#013;&#010;waLOCAL, waSETLOCAL, waCLEARLOCAL and waRetrieve in the Delphi source for this application. Requires WebHub v2.039+&lt;/p&gt;"/><ROW RowState="10" Code="16" Identifier="defCinnamonPart4" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon is principally employed in cookery as a condiment and flavouring material, being largely used in the preparation of some kinds of chocolate and liqueurs. In medicine it acts like other volatile oils and once had a reputation as a &quot;cure&quot; for colds. The pungent taste and scent come from cinnamic aldehyde or cinnamaldehyde.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The best cinnamon is from Sri Lanka, but the tree is also grown at Tellicherry, in Java, Sumatra, the West Indies, Brazil, and Egypt. Sri Lanka cinnamon of fine quality is a very thin smooth bark, with a light-yellowish brown colour, a highly fragrant odour, and a peculiarly sweet, warm and pleasing aromatic taste. Its flavour is due to an aromatic oil which it contains to the extent of from 0.5 to 1%. This essential oil, as an article of commerce, is prepared by roughly pounding the bark, macerating it in sea-water, and then quickly distilling the whole. It is of a golden-yellow colour, with the peculiar odour of cinnamon and a very hot aromatic taste. It consists essentially of cinnamic aldehyde and, by the absorption of oxygen as it ages, darkens in colour and develops resinous compounds.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon has been known from remote antiquity, and it was so highly prized among ancient nations that it was regarded as a present fit for monarchs and other great potentates. It is mentioned in Exodus 30: 23, where Moses is commanded to use both sweet (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~)  (Kinnamon) and cassia, and in Proverbs 7: 17-18, where the lover&apos;s bed is perfumed with myrrh, aloe and (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~). It is also alluded to by Herodotus and other classical writers.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Being a much more costly spice than cassia, that comparatively harsh-flavoured substance is frequently substituted for or added to it. The two barks when whole are easily enough distinguished, and their microscopic characteristics are also quite distinct. When powdered bark is treated with tincture of iodine (a test for starch), little effect is visible in the case of pure cinnamon of good quality, but when cassia is present a deep-blue tint is produced, the intensity of the coloration depending on the proportion of the cassia.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Culpepper&apos;s Herbal advises a daily draught of cinnamon in &quot;any convenient liquor&quot; against scurvy. Studies have found that using half a teaspoon of cinnamon a day significantly reduces blood sugar levels in diabetics. The benefit, which can even be produced by soaking (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~) in tea, also benefits non-diabetics who have blood sugar problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;WebHub note: the purpose of this &quot;cinnamon&quot; example is to demonstrate one technique of creating variables that are local to any named piece of W-HTML.  Please see the web actions named &#013;&#010;waLOCAL, waSETLOCAL, waCLEARLOCAL and waRetrieve in the Delphi source for this application. Requires WebHub v2.039+&lt;/p&gt;"/><ROW RowState="9" Code="11" Identifier="defCinnamon" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="(~waRetrieve.execute|defCinnamonDetail~)&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon is principally employed in cookery as a condiment and flavouring material, being largely used in the preparation of some kinds of chocolate and liqueurs. In medicine it acts like other volatile oils and once had a reputation as a &quot;cure&quot; for colds. The pungent taste and scent come from cinnamic aldehyde or cinnamaldehyde.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The best cinnamon is from Sri Lanka, but the tree is also grown at Tellicherry, in Java, Sumatra, the West Indies, Brazil, and Egypt. Sri Lanka cinnamon of fine quality is a very thin smooth bark, with a light-yellowish brown colour, a highly fragrant odour, and a peculiarly sweet, warm and pleasing aromatic taste. Its flavour is due to an aromatic oil which it contains to the extent of from 0.5 to 1%. This essential oil, as an article of commerce, is prepared by roughly pounding the bark, macerating it in sea-water, and then quickly distilling the whole. It is of a golden-yellow colour, with the peculiar odour of cinnamon and a very hot aromatic taste. It consists essentially of cinnamic aldehyde and, by the absorption of oxygen as it ages, darkens in colour and develops resinous compounds.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon has been known from remote antiquity, and it was so highly prized among ancient nations that it was regarded as a present fit for monarchs and other great potentates. It is mentioned in Exodus 30: 23, where Moses is commanded to use both sweet (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~)  (Kinnamon) and cassia, and in Proverbs 7: 17-18, where the lover&apos;s bed is perfumed with myrrh, aloe and (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~). It is also alluded to by Herodotus and other classical writers.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Being a much more costly spice than cassia, that comparatively harsh-flavoured substance is frequently substituted for or added to it. The two barks when whole are easily enough distinguished, and their microscopic characteristics are also quite distinct. When powdered bark is treated with tincture of iodine (a test for starch), little effect is visible in the case of pure cinnamon of good quality, but when cassia is present a deep-blue tint is produced, the intensity of the coloration depending on the proportion of the cassia.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Culpepper&apos;s Herbal advises a daily draught of cinnamon in &quot;any convenient liquor&quot; against scurvy. Studies have found that using half a teaspoon of cinnamon a day significantly reduces blood sugar levels in diabetics. The benefit, which can even be produced by soaking (~waLOCAL|cinnamon~) in tea, also benefits non-diabetics who have blood sugar problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;"/><ROW RowState="8" Code="11" Identifier="defCinnamon" WhenToLoad="n/a" Type="n/a" Text="&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon is principally employed in cookery as a condiment and flavouring material, being largely used in the preparation of some kinds of chocolate and liqueurs. In medicine it acts like other volatile oils and once had a reputation as a &quot;cure&quot; for colds. The pungent taste and scent come from cinnamic aldehyde or cinnamaldehyde.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;The best cinnamon is from Sri Lanka, but the tree is also grown at Tellicherry, in Java, Sumatra, the West Indies, Brazil, and Egypt. Sri Lanka cinnamon of fine quality is a very thin smooth bark, with a light-yellowish brown colour, a highly fragrant odour, and a peculiarly sweet, warm and pleasing aromatic taste. Its flavour is due to an aromatic oil which it contains to the extent of from 0.5 to 1%. This essential oil, as an article of commerce, is prepared by roughly pounding the bark, macerating it in sea-water, and then quickly distilling the whole. It is of a golden-yellow colour, with the peculiar odour of cinnamon and a very hot aromatic taste. It consists essentially of cinnamic aldehyde and, by the absorption of oxygen as it ages, darkens in colour and develops resinous compounds.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon has been known from remote antiquity, and it was so highly prized among ancient nations that it was regarded as a present fit for monarchs and other great potentates. It is mentioned in Exodus 30: 23, where Moses is commanded to use both sweet cinnamon (Kinnamon) and cassia, and in Proverbs 7: 17-18, where the lover&apos;s bed is perfumed with myrrh, aloe and cinnamon. It is also alluded to by Herodotus and other classical writers.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Being a much more costly spice than cassia, that comparatively harsh-flavoured substance is frequently substituted for or added to it. The two barks when whole are easily enough distinguished, and their microscopic characteristics are also quite distinct. When powdered bark is treated with tincture of iodine (a test for starch), little effect is visible in the case of pure cinnamon of good quality, but when cassia is present a deep-blue tint is produced, the intensity of the coloration depending on the proportion of the cassia.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;&#013;&#010;&lt;p&gt;Culpepper&apos;s Herbal advises a daily draught of cinnamon in &quot;any convenient liquor&quot; against scurvy. Studies have found that using half a teaspoon of cinnamon a day significantly reduces blood sugar levels in diabetics. The benefit, which can even be produced by soaking cinnamon in tea, also benefits non-diabetics who have blood sugar problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#013;&#010;"/></ROWDATA></DATAPACKET>